Guide to the Polly Shackleton papers, 1894-1997 MS2031
Special Collections Research Center, The George Washington University
- Alphabetical files, 1975-1986; Series 8
  - Alpha files Q-Z, numerical, 1975-1986; Series 8 Subseries 3
    - Sessions (1), 1979; Series 8 Subseries 3 (Box 25, Folder 46)
    - Sessions (2), 1979; Series 8 Subseries 3 (Box 25, Folder 47)
    - Sessions (3), 1979; Series 8 Subseries 3 (Box 25, Folder 48)
    - Shackleton Press Releases, 1978; Series 8 Subseries 3 (Box 25, Folder 10)
    - Shackleton Statements, 1986; Series 8 Subseries 3 (Box 56, Folder 33)
    - "Shoe" Ward 3 day care facility, 1981; Series 8 Subseries 3 (Box 56, Folder 1)
    - Six School Complex 10th Anniversary Recognition Resolution, 1984; Series 8 Subseries 3 (Box 25, Folder 30)
    - Six Schools Complex, 1977-1978; Series 8 Subseries 3 (Box 56, Folder 2)
    - Smoking Bill III, 1984; Series 8 Subseries 3 (Box 17, Folder 12)
    - Social Services, Undated; Series 8 Subseries 3 (Box 20, Folder 8)
    - Speech by Polly Shackleton, 1978; Series 8 Subseries 3 (Box 18, Folder 7)
    - St. Columbia's Episcopal Church SEnior High Youth Group Recy. Res., 1985; Series 8 Subseries 3 (Box 52, Folder 5)
    - St. Elizabeth's Hearing, 1979; Series 8 Subseries 3 (Box 15, Folder 4)
    - St. Elizabeth's Hospital, 1975-1976; Series 8 Subseries 3 (Box 28, Folder 1)
    - State Department, 1984; Series 8 Subseries 3 (Box 39, Folder 19)
    - Statehood, 1980-1981; Series 8 Subseries 3 (Box 28, Folder 23)
    - Statements by Shackleton, 1985; Series 8 Subseries 3 (Box 56, Folder 34)
    - Statements Clips for issues, etc, 1982; Series 8 Subseries 3 (Box 31, Folder 1)
    - Statements Clips for issues, etc, 1982; Series 8 Subseries 3 (Box 31, Folder 2)
    - Supplies - (Memos - Requisitions), 1974-1986; Series 8 Subseries 3 (Box 56, Folder 3)
    - Surplus Property, 1981-1982; Series 8 Subseries 3 (Box 17, Folder 8)
    - Tags - Low Numbered Registrations, 1975-1986; Series 8 Subseries 3 (Box 56, Folder 4)
    - Tax Rates - Comparison with DC, 1982; Series 8 Subseries 3 (Box 17, Folder 7)
    - Tax Revision Commission, 1976; Series 8 Subseries 3 (Box 28, Folder 3)
    - Taxes (General), 1974-1979; Series 8 Subseries 3 (Box 28, Folder 2)
    - Tenley Library Council, 1977; Series 8 Subseries 3 (Box 56, Folder 7)
    - Testimony - Polly, 1975; Series 8 Subseries 3 (Box 28, Folder 4)
    - Thank Yous - Post Primary + General Election, 1975; Series 8 Subseries 3 (Box 28, Folder 6)
    - Thank Yous - Post Primary + General Election, 1975; Series 8 Subseries 3 (Box 28, Folder 7)
    - The Brandywine - 4545 Connecticut Ave., 1979; Series 8 Subseries 3 (Box 27, Folder 10)
    - The Capital Club (Senior Citizens), 1974; Series 8 Subseries 3 (Box 1, Folder 21)
    - The Residency Exemption Emergency Act, 1981; Series 8 Subseries 3 (Box 25, Folder 41)
    - Time & Attendance, 1985; Series 8 Subseries 3 (Box 20, Folder 16)
    - Time & Attendance, 1984; Series 8 Subseries 3 (Box 20, Folder 17)
    - Time & Attendance, 1983; Series 8 Subseries 3 (Box 20, Folder 18)
    - Time & Attendance, 1982; Series 8 Subseries 3 (Box 20, Folder 19)
    - Time & Attendance, 1986; Series 8 Subseries 3 (Box 20, Folder 21)
    - Traffic - American University Park, 1978-1984; Series 8 Subseries 3 (Box 56, Folder 5)
    - Transportation, 1974-1976; Series 8 Subseries 3 (Box 28, Folder 5)
    - Transportation Planning Ward 3, 1977-1978; Series 8 Subseries 3 (Box 18, Folder 6)
    - Tregaron, 1982; Series 8 Subseries 3 (Box 56, Folder 6)
    - Trucks & Tour Buses - Parking Problem and Duke Ellington Bridge, 1977-1985; Series 8 Subseries 3 (Box 56, Folder 8)
    - Unemployment Compensation, 1973-1978; Series 8 Subseries 3 (Box 14, Folder 10)
    - Unemployment Compensation, 1978; Series 8 Subseries 3 (Box 14, Folder 11)
    - Unemployment Compensation, 1980; Series 8 Subseries 3 (Box 17, Folder 1)
    - Unemployment Compensation Act, 1982; Series 8 Subseries 3 (Box 17, Folder 6)
    - Unemployment Compensation Study Commission, 1983; Series 8 Subseries 3 (Box 17, Folder 5)
    - United Planning Organization, 1983; Series 8 Subseries 3 (Box 28, Folder 11)
    - University Legal Services (hon.bd.member), 1977; Series 8 Subseries 3 (Box 28, Folder 9)
    - University of District of Columbia, 1983; Series 8 Subseries 3 (Box 28, Folder 8)
    - Uptown Citizen, 1975; Series 8 Subseries 3 (Box 56, Folder 9)
    - Urban League - Washington, 1977-1983; Series 8 Subseries 3 (Box 28, Folder 10)
    - Utilities, 1981-1983; Series 8 Subseries 3 (Box 17, Folder 4)
    - Utilities - C&P Rate Increase, 1983; Series 8 Subseries 3 (Box 17, Folder 3)
    - Van Ness - South & East, 1980-1983; Series 8 Subseries 3 (Box 56, Folder 11)
    - Vending, 1975-1977; Series 8 Subseries 3 (Box 16, Folder 7)
    - Vendors, 1975-1980; Series 8 Subseries 3 (Box 28, Folder 13)
    - Volunteers, 1977; Series 8 Subseries 3 (Box 56, Folder 12)
    - Wanda Washburn, 1983-1986; Series 8 Subseries 3 (Box 56, Folder 10)
    - Ward 3 Board of Education, 1981; Series 8 Subseries 3 (Box 28, Folder 38)
    - Ward 3 Democratic Committee, 1976-1985; Series 8 Subseries 3 (Box 28, Folder 35)
    - Ward 3 Food Stamp Office, 1975-1976; Series 8 Subseries 3 (Box 28, Folder 37)
    - Ward 3 Office - General Correspondence, 1983; Series 8 Subseries 3 (Box 20, Folder 22)
    - Ward 3 Parks: Lafayette, Forest Hills, 1977; Series 8 Subseries 3 (Box 18, Folder 2)
    - Ward 3 Recreation (1 of 7), 1979-1981; Series 8 Subseries 3 (Box 23, Folder 28)
    - Ward 3 Recreation (2 of 7), 1979; Series 8 Subseries 3 (Box 23, Folder 29)
    - Ward 3 Recreation (3 of 7), 1978-1979; Series 8 Subseries 3 (Box 23, Folder 30)
    - Ward 3 Recreation (4 of 7), 1978-1979; Series 8 Subseries 3 (Box 23, Folder 31)
    - Ward 3 Recreation (5 of 7), 1978; Series 8 Subseries 3 (Box 23, Folder 32)
    - Ward 3 Recreation (6 of 7), 1978; Series 8 Subseries 3 (Box 23, Folder 33)
    - Ward 3 Recreation (7 of 7), 1977; Series 8 Subseries 3 (Box 23, Folder 34)
    - Ward 3 Task Force, 1975-1978; Series 8 Subseries 3 (Box 55, Folder 2)
    - Ward 3 Task Force, 1975-1978; Series 8 Subseries 3 (Box 55, Folder 3)
    - Ward 3 Task Force on Aging, 1975-1977; Series 8 Subseries 3 (Box 55, Folder 6)
    - Ward 3 Task Force on Recreation (1 of 3), 1975; Series 8 Subseries 3 (Box 23, Folder 24)
    - Ward 3 Task Force on Recreation (2 of 3), 1975; Series 8 Subseries 3 (Box 23, Folder 25)
    - Ward 3 Task Force on Recreation (3 of 3), 1975; Series 8 Subseries 3 (Box 23, Folder 26)
    - Ward 3 Vending, 1983-1984; Series 8 Subseries 3 (Box 56, Folder 13)
    - Ward III Plans, Undated; Series 8 Subseries 3 (Box 21a, Folder 9)
    - Ward Office Log, 1983; Series 8 Subseries 3 (Box 21a, Folder 2)
    - Washington Hospital Center, 1978; Series 8 Subseries 3 (Box 28, Folder 14)
    - Washington Post - General, 1984; Series 8 Subseries 3 (Box 28, Folder 15)
    - Washington Teachers Union, 1981; Series 8 Subseries 3 (Box 28, Folder 16)
    - Washington Technical Institution, 1975; Series 8 Subseries 3 (Box 28, Folder 17)
    - Water Resources, 1977; Series 8 Subseries 3 (Box 28, Folder 25)
    - White House Conference on Families, 1980; Series 8 Subseries 3 (Box 28, Folder 18)
    - Whitehurst Freeway, 1983; Series 8 Subseries 3 (Box 14, Folder 4)
    - Whitehurst Freeway, 1982; Series 8 Subseries 3 (Box 14, Folder 5)
    - Whitehurst Freeway, 1983; Series 8 Subseries 3 (Box 28, Folder 19)
    - Wider Opportunities for Women, 1975-1983; Series 8 Subseries 3 (Box 28, Folder 20)
    - Wilson Swimming Pool, 1981-1984; Series 8 Subseries 3 (Box 56, Folder 14)
    - Wisconsin Ave. Corridor Committee, 1977; Series 8 Subseries 3 (Box 18, Folder 12)
    - Wisconsin Ave. Corridor Committee, 1975; Series 8 Subseries 3 (Box 18, Folder 13)
    - Wisconsin Ave. Corridor Committee, 1978-1985; Series 8 Subseries 3 (Box 18, Folder 18)
    - Women, 1977-1983; Series 8 Subseries 3 (Box 14, Folder 6)
    - Women, 1977-1979; Series 8 Subseries 3 (Box 14, Folder 7)
    - Women, 1976-1977; Series 8 Subseries 3 (Box 14, Folder 8)
    - Women, 1975; Series 8 Subseries 3 (Box 14, Folder 9)
    - Women International Womens Year (IWy), 1975-1983; Series 8 Subseries 3 (Box 28, Folder 21)
    - Workman's Comp, 1979-1980; Series 8 Subseries 3 (Box 31, Folder 14)
    - Youth for Understanding, 1979-1986; Series 8 Subseries 3 (Box 28, Folder 22)
    - Zoning, 1977-1979; Series 8 Subseries 3 (Box 20, Folder 6)
    - Zoning - Cat's Pajamas Case, 1982-1983; Series 8 Subseries 3 (Box 17, Folder 2)
    - Zoning Hearing, 1978; Series 8 Subseries 3 (Box 20, Folder 5)
    - 5-11 Nancy Hanks Center, 1983; Series 8 Subseries 3 (Box 25, Folder 25)
    - 5-132 Ward 3 Task Force On ANCs, 1983; Series 8 Subseries 3 (Box 25, Folder 21)
    - 5-176 Older Americans Day, 1983; Series 8 Subseries 3 (Box 25, Folder 20)
    - 5-196 Hurray For Children Day, 1983; Series 8 Subseries 3 (Box 25, Folder 19)
    - 5-2 Charles Drew Bridge, 1983; Series 8 Subseries 3 (Box 25, Folder 15)
    - 5-22 Drunk Driving Federal Conformity Amendment Act, 1983; Series 8 Subseries 3 (Box 25, Folder 32)
    - 5-379 "Building Code Violation Citation and Lein Creation Act of 1984", 1984-1985; Series 8 Subseries 3 (Box 8, Folder 2)
    - 5-70 Prohibit Sale Alcohol at Gas Stations Act, 1983; Series 8 Subseries 3 (Box 25, Folder 23)
    - 5-91 Nursing Home Residents Day, 1983; Series 8 Subseries 3 (Box 25, Folder 22)
    - 6-61 "Motor Vehicle Parking Regulation Amend. Act", 1985; Series 8 Subseries 3 (Box 52, Folder 3)
- Office files, 1968-1986; Series 9
  Organized into 4 subseries: Files A-C, Files D-H, Files I-P, and Files R-Y.
  The series contains the type of records found in subject files and covers the date range from 1968 - 1986.
  - Office files A-C, 1968-1986; Series 9 Subseries 1
    - Aging (1 of 5), 1968 March 15; Series 9 Subseries 1 (Box 4, Folder 1)
    - Aging (2 of 5), 1969; Series 9 Subseries 1 (Box 4, Folder 2)
    - Aging (3 of 5), 1969; Series 9 Subseries 1 (Box 4, Folder 3)
    - Aging (4 of 5), 1970; Series 9 Subseries 1 (Box 4, Folder 4)
    - Aging (5 of 5), 1970-1971; Series 9 Subseries 1 (Box 4, Folder 5)
    - AIA, 1962; Series 9 Subseries 1 (Box 4, Folder 5)
    - Air Pollution (1 of 2), 1969; Series 9 Subseries 1 (Box 4, Folder 6)
    - Air Pollution (2 of 2), 1969; Series 9 Subseries 1 (Box 4, Folder 7)
    - Airplane Flight Patterns, 1980; Series 9 Subseries 1 (Box 34, Folder 2)
    - Anacostia Neighborhood Mueum, 1968; Series 9 Subseries 1 (Box 4, Folder 8)
    - ANC 3F, 1976-1977; Series 9 Subseries 1 (Box 59, Folder 11)
    - ANC 3G, 1976-1977; Series 9 Subseries 1 (Box 59, Folder 12)
    - ANC-SMD: Potential Candidates, 1975-1976; Series 9 Subseries 1 (Box 57, Folder 3)
    - ANCs Government Information Set-Up, 1976-1980; Series 9 Subseries 1 (Box 57, Folder 6)
    - Appointment Book, 1983; Series 9 Subseries 1 (Box 9, Folder 10)
    - Appointment Diary, 1975; Series 9 Subseries 1 (Box 9, Folder 1)
    - Appointment Diary, 1976; Series 9 Subseries 1 (Box 9, Folder 2)
    - Appointment Diary, 1977; Series 9 Subseries 1 (Box 9, Folder 3)
    - Appointment Diary, 1978; Series 9 Subseries 1 (Box 9, Folder 5)
    - Appointment Diary, 1979; Series 9 Subseries 1 (Box 9, Folder 6)
    - Appointment Diary, 1980; Series 9 Subseries 1 (Box 9, Folder 7)
    - Appointment Diary, 1981; Series 9 Subseries 1 (Box 9, Folder 8)
    - Appointment Diary, 1982; Series 9 Subseries 1 (Box 9, Folder 9)
    - Appointments, 1986; Series 9 Subseries 1 (Box 33, Folder 10)
    - Asst. City Administrator for Planning and Development, 1979-1984; Series 9 Subseries 1 (Box 53, Folder 6)
    - Auditor Reports and Notes, 1975; Series 9 Subseries 1 (Box 74, Folder 1)
    - Beverage Containers, 1975; Series 9 Subseries 1 (Box 49, Folder 6)
    - Bill 6-195, 1986; Series 9 Subseries 1 (Box 10, Folder 8)
    - Bill 6-195 Minimum Protection for Drug & Alcohol Abuse & Mental Illness, 1986; Series 9 Subseries 1 (Box 53, Folder 4)
    - Binder Related to Water Supply, 1982-1984; Series 9 Subseries 1 (Box 36, Folder 13)
    - Biological Notes, Undated; Series 9 Subseries 1 (Box 4, Folder 9)
    - Black United Front, 1969; Series 9 Subseries 1 (Box 4, Folder 10)
    - Board of Education, 1983-1984; Series 9 Subseries 1 (Box 48, Folder 13)
    - Board of Elections & Ethics, 1986; Series 9 Subseries 1 (Box 35, Folder 6)
    - Board of Elections & Ethics, 1983-1986; Series 9 Subseries 1 (Box 48, Folder 9)
    - Bottle Bill & Resource Recovery, 1975; Series 9 Subseries 1 (Box 49, Folder 8)
    - Budget, 1979; Series 9 Subseries 1 (Box 38, Folder 8)
    - Budget Adjustment (1 of 2), 1980; Series 9 Subseries 1 (Box 19, Folder 13)
    - Budget Adjustment (2 of 2), 1980; Series 9 Subseries 1 (Box 19, Folder 14)
    - Budget Amendment, 1980; Series 9 Subseries 1 (Box 3, Folder 12)
    - Budget Hearings Committee on the Judiciary, 1979; Series 9 Subseries 1 (Box 38, Folder 13)
    - Budget Hearings Committee on the Judiciary, 1979; Series 9 Subseries 1 (Box 38, Folder 14)
    - Budget Markup, 1979; Series 9 Subseries 1 (Box 38, Folder 17)
    - Budget Supplemental and Budget Adjustments, 1980; Series 9 Subseries 1 (Box 38, Folder 20)
    - Business and Economic Development, 1979-1986; Series 9 Subseries 1 (Box 48, Folder 18)
    - C & P Rate, 1985; Series 9 Subseries 1 (Box 57, Folder 18)
    - Cable Television System Franchise Invitation for Applications, 1983; Series 9 Subseries 1 (Box 43, Folder 1)
    - Cable TV, 1981; Series 9 Subseries 1 (Box 54, Folder 5)
    - Cable TV, 1982; Series 9 Subseries 1 (Box 54, Folder 4)
    - Cable TV (1 of 17), 1984; Series 9 Subseries 1 (Box 5, Folder 5)
    - Cable TV (2 of 17), 1984; Series 9 Subseries 1 (Box 5, Folder 6)
    - Cable TV (3 of 17), 1984; Series 9 Subseries 1 (Box 5, Folder 7)
    - Cable TV (4 of 17), 1984; Series 9 Subseries 1 (Box 5, Folder 8)
    - Cable TV (5 of 17), 1984; Series 9 Subseries 1 (Box 5, Folder 9)
    - Cable TV (6 of 17), 1984; Series 9 Subseries 1 (Box 5, Folder 10)
    - Cable TV (7 of 17), 1984; Series 9 Subseries 1 (Box 5, Folder 11)
    - Cable TV (8 of 17), 1984; Series 9 Subseries 1 (Box 5, Folder 12)
    - Cable TV (9 of 17), 1984; Series 9 Subseries 1 (Box 5, Folder 13)
    - Cable TV (10 of 17), 1984; Series 9 Subseries 1 (Box 5, Folder 14)
    - Cable TV (11 of 17), 1984; Series 9 Subseries 1 (Box 5, Folder 15)
    - Cable TV (12 of 17), 1984; Series 9 Subseries 1 (Box 5, Folder 16)
    - Cable TV (13 of 17), 1984; Series 9 Subseries 1 (Box 5, Folder 17)
    - Cable TV (14 of 17), 1984; Series 9 Subseries 1 (Box 5, Folder 18)
    - Cable TV (15 of 17), 1984; Series 9 Subseries 1 (Box 5, Folder 19)
    - Cable TV (16 of 17), 1982; Series 9 Subseries 1 (Box 5, Folder 20)
    - Cable TV (17 of 17), 1984; Series 9 Subseries 1 (Box 5, Folder 21)
    - Cable TV Letters: Constituent, Lobby (1 of 4), 1984; Series 9 Subseries 1 (Box 5, Folder 1)
    - Cable TV Letters: Constituent, Lobby (2 of 4), 1984; Series 9 Subseries 1 (Box 5, Folder 2)
    - Cable TV Letters: Constituent, Lobby (3 of 4), 1984; Series 9 Subseries 1 (Box 5, Folder 3)
    - Cable TV Letters: Constituent, Lobby (4 of 4), 1984; Series 9 Subseries 1 (Box 5, Folder 4)
    - Ceremonial Resolution, 1980; Series 9 Subseries 1 (Box 142, Folder 1)
    - Child Day Care Association, Inc. (1 of 11), 1968-1969; Series 9 Subseries 1 (Box 4, Folder 12)
    - Child Day Care Association, Inc. (2 of 11), 1968-1969; Series 9 Subseries 1 (Box 4, Folder 13)
    - Child Day Care Association, Inc. (3 of 11), 1969; Series 9 Subseries 1 (Box 4, Folder 14)
    - Child Day Care Association, Inc. (4 of 11), 1969; Series 9 Subseries 1 (Box 4, Folder 15)
    - Child Day Care Association, Inc. (5 of 11), 1969; Series 9 Subseries 1 (Box 4, Folder 16)
    - Child Day Care Association, Inc. (6 of 11), 1969; Series 9 Subseries 1 (Box 4, Folder 17)
    - Child Day Care Association, Inc. (7 of 11), 1968-1969; Series 9 Subseries 1 (Box 4, Folder 18)
    - Child Day Care Association, Inc. (8 of 11), 1968; Series 9 Subseries 1 (Box 4, Folder 19)
    - Child Day Care Association, Inc. (9 of 11), 1968; Series 9 Subseries 1 (Box 4, Folder 20)
    - Child Day Care Association, Inc. (10 of 11), 1969; Series 9 Subseries 1 (Box 4, Folder 21)
    - Child Day Care Association, Inc. (11 of 11), 1968; Series 9 Subseries 1 (Box 4, Folder 22)
    - Chron. File, 1982; Series 9 Subseries 1 (Box 57, Folder 11)
    - Chron. File, 1982; Series 9 Subseries 1 (Box 57, Folder 12)
    - Chron. File, 1982; Series 9 Subseries 1 (Box 57, Folder 13)
    - Chron. File, 1982; Series 9 Subseries 1 (Box 57, Folder 14)
    - Chron. File, 1983; Series 9 Subseries 1 (Box 57, Folder 15)
    - Citizens and Civil Groups and PTA Misc., 1975-1986; Series 9 Subseries 1 (Box 47, Folder 4)
    - Citizens Information Service, 1968; Series 9 Subseries 1 (Box 4, Folder 25)
    - City Administration, 1979-1982; Series 9 Subseries 1 (Box 53, Folder 15)
    - City Hall Complaint Center, 1968; Series 9 Subseries 1 (Box 4, Folder 23)
    - Commission on the Arts, 1968; Series 9 Subseries 1 (Box 4, Folder 24)
    - Committee of the Whole (1 of 4), 1975; Series 9 Subseries 1 (Box 13, Folder 11)
    - Committee of the Whole (2 of 4), 1975; Series 9 Subseries 1 (Box 13, Folder 12)
    - Committee of the Whole (3 of 4), 1975; Series 9 Subseries 1 (Box 13, Folder 13)
    - Committee of the Whole (4 of 4), 1975; Series 9 Subseries 1 (Box 13, Folder 14)
    - Committee on Government Operations, 1982; Series 9 Subseries 1 (Box 44, Folder 1)
    - Committee on Government Operations, 1981; Series 9 Subseries 1 (Box 59, Folder 2)
    - Committee on Government Operations, 1981; Series 9 Subseries 1 (Box 59, Folder 3)
    - Committee on Highways and Transportation (1 of 2), 1969; Series 9 Subseries 1 (Box 4, Folder 26)
    - Committee on Highways and Transportation (2 of 2), 1968; Series 9 Subseries 1 (Box 4, Folder 27)
    - Committee on Housing and Human Development (1 of 2), 1968-1969; Series 9 Subseries 1 (Box 4, Folder 28)
    - Committee on Housing and Human Development (2 of 2), 1968-1969; Series 9 Subseries 1 (Box 4, Folder 29)
    - Committee on Human Resources General (1 of 5), 1979; Series 9 Subseries 1 (Box 19, Folder 16)
    - Committee on Human Resources General (2 of 5), 1979; Series 9 Subseries 1 (Box 19, Folder 17)
    - Committee on Human Resources General (3 of 5), 1979; Series 9 Subseries 1 (Box 19, Folder 18)
    - Committee on Human Resources General (4 of 5), 1979; Series 9 Subseries 1 (Box 19, Folder 19)
    - Committee on Human Resources General (5 of 5), 1979; Series 9 Subseries 1 (Box 19, Folder 20)
    - Committee on Human Services General (1 of 3), 1980; Series 9 Subseries 1 (Box 19, Folder 10)
    - Committee on Human Services General (2 of 3), 1980; Series 9 Subseries 1 (Box 19, Folder 11)
    - Committee on Human Services General (3 of 3), 1980; Series 9 Subseries 1 (Box 19, Folder 12)
    - Committee on Recreation and Youth Programs (1 of 7), 1969; Series 9 Subseries 1 (Box 4, Folder 30)
    - Committee on Recreation and Youth Programs (2 of 7), 1969; Series 9 Subseries 1 (Box 4, Folder 31)
    - Committee on Recreation and Youth Programs (3 of 7), 1969; Series 9 Subseries 1 (Box 4, Folder 32)
    - Committee on Recreation and Youth Programs (4 of 7), 1969; Series 9 Subseries 1 (Box 4, Folder 33)
    - Committee on Recreation and Youth Programs (5 of 7), 1967-1969; Series 9 Subseries 1 (Box 4, Folder 34)
    - Committee on Recreation and Youth Programs (6 of 7), 1969; Series 9 Subseries 1 (Box 4, Folder 35)
    - Committee on Recreation and Youth Programs (7 of 7), 1969; Series 9 Subseries 1 (Box 4, Folder 36)
    - Committee on Transportation and Environmental Affairs, 1976; Series 9 Subseries 1 (Box 49, Folder 4)
    - Committee on Transportation and Environmental Affairs, 1975; Series 9 Subseries 1 (Box 49, Folder 5)
    - Community Services, 1984-1986; Series 9 Subseries 1 (Box 13, Folder 1)
    - Community-Group Health Foundation, Inc. ( of 3), 1968; Series 9 Subseries 1 (Box 4, Folder 38)
    - Community-Group Health Foundation, Inc. (1 of 3), 1968-1969; Series 9 Subseries 1 (Box 4, Folder 37)
    - Community-Group Health Foundation, Inc. (3 of 3), 1968; Series 9 Subseries 1 (Box 4, Folder 39)
    - Comp Plan (1 of 3), 1983; Series 9 Subseries 1 (Box 36, Folder 1)
    - Comp Plan (2 of 3), 1983; Series 9 Subseries 1 (Box 36, Folder 2)
    - Comp Plan (3 of 3), 1983; Series 9 Subseries 1 (Box 36, Folder 3)
    - Comp. Plan Correspondence, etc., 1982; Series 9 Subseries 1 (Box 50, Folder 1)
    - Comp. Plan Correspondence, etc., 1977; Series 9 Subseries 1 (Box 50, Folder 2)
    - Comp. Plan Correspondence, etc., 1976; Series 9 Subseries 1 (Box 50, Folder 3)
    - Comp. Plan Correspondence, etc., 1975; Series 9 Subseries 1 (Box 50, Folder 4)
    - Complaint Center, 1979; Series 9 Subseries 1 (Box 53, Folder 7)
    - Consumer & Regulatory Affairs, 1986; Series 9 Subseries 1 (Box 35, Folder 2)
    - Consumer Affairs, 1975; Series 9 Subseries 1 (Box 48, Folder 15)
    - Corporation Councel (1 of 3), 1986; Series 9 Subseries 1 (Box 13, Folder 2)
    - Corporation Councel (2 of 3), 1986; Series 9 Subseries 1 (Box 13, Folder 3)
    - Corporation Councel (3 of 3), 1986; Series 9 Subseries 1 (Box 13, Folder 4)
    - Corporation Counsel, 1976-1986; Series 9 Subseries 1 (Box 48, Folder 17)
    - Correspondence/Budget, 1979; Series 9 Subseries 1 (Box 38, Folder 18)
    - Councel Memos/News Releases, 1978; Series 9 Subseries 1 (Box 13, Folder 17)
    - Council Committees, 1978-1984; Series 9 Subseries 1 (Box 10, Folder 5)
    - Council of Governements, 1984-1985; Series 9 Subseries 1 (Box 48, Folder 19)
    - Council Parking Lot, 1978-1979; Series 9 Subseries 1 (Box 32, Folder 30)
    - Council Secretary, 1975-1979; Series 9 Subseries 1 (Box 13, Folder 37)
    - Council Secretary, 1982; Series 9 Subseries 1 (Box 13, Folder 38)
    - Council Secretary (1 of 3), 1983-1985; Series 9 Subseries 1 (Box 13, Folder 31)
    - Council Secretary (2 of 3), 1983-1985; Series 9 Subseries 1 (Box 13, Folder 32)
    - Council Secretary (3 of 3), 1983-1985; Series 9 Subseries 1 (Box 13, Folder 33)
    - Council Staffing, 1979-1982; Series 9 Subseries 1 (Box 58, Folder 3)
    - Councilmember Shackleton, 1975; Series 9 Subseries 1 (Box 59, Folder 10)
    - Councilmembers Literature, 1975-1980; Series 9 Subseries 1 (Box 32, Folder 31)
    - Councilwoman Polly Shackleton, 1975-1977; Series 9 Subseries 1 (Box 59, Folder 14)
    - Councilwoman Shackleton (Personal) (1 of 16), 1970; Series 9 Subseries 1 (Box 60, Folder 10)
    - Councilwoman Shackleton (Personal) (2 of 16), 1970; Series 9 Subseries 1 (Box 60, Folder 11)
    - Councilwoman Shackleton (Personal) (3 of 16), 1970; Series 9 Subseries 1 (Box 60, Folder 12)
    - Councilwoman Shackleton (Personal) (4 of 16), 1968-1970; Series 9 Subseries 1 (Box 60, Folder 13)
    - Councilwoman Shackleton (Personal) (5 of 16), 1969; Series 9 Subseries 1 (Box 60, Folder 14)
    - Councilwoman Shackleton (Personal) (6 of 16), 1969; Series 9 Subseries 1 (Box 60, Folder 15)
    - Councilwoman Shackleton (Personal) (7 of 16), 1969; Series 9 Subseries 1 (Box 60, Folder 16)
    - Councilwoman Shackleton (Personal) (8 of 16), 1969; Series 9 Subseries 1 (Box 60, Folder 17)
    - Councilwoman Shackleton (Personal) (9 of 16), 1969; Series 9 Subseries 1 (Box 60, Folder 18)
    - Councilwoman Shackleton (Personal) (10 of 16), 1969; Series 9 Subseries 1 (Box 60, Folder 19)
    - Councilwoman Shackleton (Personal) (11 of 16), 1969; Series 9 Subseries 1 (Box 60, Folder 20)
    - Councilwoman Shackleton (Personal) (12 of 16), 1969; Series 9 Subseries 1 (Box 60, Folder 21)
    - Councilwoman Shackleton (Personal) (13 of 16), 1968-1969; Series 9 Subseries 1 (Box 60, Folder 22)
    - Councilwoman Shackleton (Personal) (14 of 16), 1968-1969; Series 9 Subseries 1 (Box 60, Folder 23)